novelgames.com 2012-05-21

# Novel Games - Privacy Statement

We respect your privacy and will try to protect it by all means. We will keep all your personal information strictly secret and will not disclose any of your personal information to any third party.

Novel Games Limited would like to show our commitment to protect your privacy through this privacy statement.

## Information Collection and Use

All personal information collected will only be used to provide better products and better services. All personal information collected will not be disclosed to any third party.

## Activity Log

Your activity within this web site will be automatically logged by the server. The information collected will only be used to analyze problems and improve our products and services. We will not disclose your personal information collected to any third party.

## Cookies

Our web site does not collect personal information through cookies.

## Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

## Security

We use industry standard methods to protect your personal information submitted through this site. When you submit information in the order form, all your personal information will be encrypted with 128 bit SSL encryption method before sending to us. All personal information sent will not be accessible to any third party.

## Buy Products

We use a third party provider to process orders, your personal information collected will only be used for billing purposes and for sending you the products. We will use the information collected to contact you if there's any need (eg. when there's a bug fix for the product), if you don't want to be contacted, simply send us a email and you will never be contacted. All personal information collected will not be disclosed to any third party.

## Contests and Prizes

There will be contests and prizes for players of our games. Your personal information collected will only be used for sending you the prizes. We will use the information collected to contact you if there's any need (eg. when there's a bug fix for the product), if you don't want to be contacted, simply send us an email and you will never be contacted. All personal information collected will not be disclosed to any third party.

## Newsletters

You only need to provide an email address to subscribe to our free newsletter. When you don't want to receive the newsletter, you can unsubscribe it and be removed from our mailing list immediatedly. All personal information collected will not be disclosed to any third party.

## Links to Other Sites

This web site contains links to other web sites. We are not responsible for the contents or the privacy practises of those web sites.
